<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Driplane on Dripline Documentation</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/</link><description>Recent content in Driplane on Dripline Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 04:15:05 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elasticsearch</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/elasticsearch/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 15:40:23 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/elasticsearch/</guid><description>ElasticSearch This filter writes on ElasticSearch all the message it receives as input and return as output the document ID.
You can also specify what message&amp;rsquo;s field it should use as input.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for filter&amp;rsquo;s output (it could be main or an extra field) .</description></item><item><title>File</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/file/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 15:33:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/file/</guid><description>File This filter get as input the path of a local file, read it and return the content back to the pipeline.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for filter&amp;rsquo;s output (it could be main or an extra field) ... | file(target=&amp;quot;file_content&amp;quot;) | ...
Output The output will contain the content of the read file.</description></item><item><title>Basics</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/basics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/basics/</guid><description>JS This filter allows to extend the basic driplane&amp;rsquo;s filter, defining Javascript scripts. It is based on islazy/plugin which in turn is based on robertkrimen/otto.
Defining a JS file with our custom logic, it is possible create a complex filter.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description path STRING empty path of the Javascript file (it can contains multiple functions) function STRING empty name of the function in the JS file to call when a Message is received .</description></item><item><title>Build and install</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/installation/build/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/installation/build/</guid><description>Build and install Launching the follow command go will take care of the downloading, the dependency resolving, the building and finally of the installation of the binary in the $GOBIN directory.
go get -u github.com/Matrix86/driplane/&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Cache</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/cache/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/cache/</guid><description>Cache This filter introduces a simple cache mechanism in the rule. It is a TTL based cache and it can have a local visibility (cache is only visible to the current filter) or a global visibility (cache shared across ALL the rules).
If the target of the Message as input has been cached before, and his TTL is not expired, it will be dropped and not propagated to the next filter.</description></item><item><title>File</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/file/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/file/</guid><description>File feeder This feeder can create the stream starting from a file. Like the tail -f command it opens the specified file and propagates a data message if a line is being added to the file.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description filename STRING empty the path of the file that it has to keep track toend BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; the feeder will start to create data messages only for new added lines .</description></item><item><title>First look</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/rules/definition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/rules/definition/</guid><description>First look Driplane include a simple language to define where to get the stream and what operation to exec, or how to filter the data.
In the rule could be defined 3 type of nodes:
FEEDER : it is the node responsible for creating of a stream of data (it reads every changes on a file, gets tweets from Twitter, etc..)
FILTER : it receives data from a feeder or another filter and checks some conditions on them or makes some changes on them.</description></item><item><title>Docker</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/installation/docker/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/installation/docker/</guid><description>Docker driplane is containerized using a really lightweight Linux distribution called Alpine Linux.
To pull the latest image version:
docker pull matrix86/driplane To run it:
docker run &amp;ndash;rm -v config:/app/config -it matrix86/driplane:latest -config config/config.yaml where the config directory contains the config.yaml file, the rule directory, the js directory and the templates directory.
Link to the Docker repository</description></item><item><title>Entrypoint</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/entrypoint/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/entrypoint/</guid><description>Entrypoint The JS file consists of one or more functions, and they can be used in different filters or in combination between them.
The function must respect some constraints:
the function&amp;rsquo;s name contained in the function parameter of the filter has to start with a capital letter; the function prototype must 3 variables; the function must return a JS object with at least the filtered field; Function&amp;rsquo;s prototype The function&amp;rsquo;s name specified in the function parameter of the filter, receives 3 input parameters:</description></item><item><title>Plugin Packages</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/packages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/packages/</guid><description>Packages Since the JS doesn&amp;rsquo;t have all the useful functions to perform operations like on file manipulation or http request (see otto docs for more info), driplane maps and export to the JS environment some Go functions as packages.
These mapped functions are not definitive and they could change over time. File This package contains functions for manipulating files.
Return The return value will be a JS object containing 2 fields:</description></item><item><title>RSS</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/rss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/rss/</guid><description>RSS This feeder creates a stream starting from a feed RSS, ATOM or JSON.
It is based on gofeed so you can refer to it for more info and supported formats.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description url STRING empty URL of the feed freq DURATION 60s how often the feed should be parsed start_from_beginning BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; it starts to parse the feed from the beginning (the first time it will ignore the pubdate field of the feed) ignore_pubdate BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; it ignores the pubdate and it returns all the feed content every time .</description></item><item><title>Syntax</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/rules/syntax/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/rules/syntax/</guid><description>Syntax The syntax of the driplane&amp;rsquo;s rules is very simple. As for the BASH every filter&amp;rsquo;s output is sent to the next filter&amp;rsquo;s input concatenating the two of them with the | character.
All the rules have to start with a name and end with a ; char.
Import Using the directive import it is possible to include one or more files and their rules in another one. All the rules defined in an included file</description></item><item><title>Twitter</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/twitter/</guid><description>Twitter This feeder creates a stream from tweets. It is possible to define the keywords, or the users to follow.
Based on go-twitter
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description consumerKey STRING empty Twitter Auth consumerSecret STRING empty Twitter Auth accessToken STRING empty Twitter Auth accessSecret STRING empty Twitter Auth keywords STRING empty comma separated keywords that should match on the tweets users STRING empty comma separated users list languages STRING empty filter by language disable_retweet BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; don&amp;rsquo;t include retweets in the stream disable_quoted BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; don&amp;rsquo;t include quoted tweets in the stream .</description></item><item><title>Web</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/web/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/web/</guid><description>Web This feeder creates a stream starting from a web page. It is possible to define how often the page should be downloaded and parsed.
Every time the page is parsed a Message is sent down the lane.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description url STRING empty URL of the web page freq DURATION 60s how often the page should be parsed text_only BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; it removes all the tags from the page method STRING &amp;ldquo;GET&amp;rdquo; HTTP method to use on the requests headers JSON empty Headers to use in the request data JSON empty POST fields to send with the requests (it&amp;rsquo;s not possible to use in combination with rawData) rawData STRING empty raw body of the requests (it&amp;rsquo;s not possible to use in combination with data) status STRING empty the filter will propagate the Message only if the returned status is this cookies STRING empty Path of the JSON file containing the cookies to use .</description></item><item><title>Slack</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/slack/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 22:05:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/slack/</guid><description>Slack This feeder creates a stream using the Slack Events API.
In order to use this feeder, you need to create a Slack App, define its Bot Token scopes and finally enable the Event Subscriptions.
The feeder will start a webserver to receive the events, so it should be reachable by slack. If you are behind a NAT or Firewall, you can enable localtunnel.
Based on slack-go/slack
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description bot_token STRING empty token Bot (starting with xoxb-*) app_token STRING empty App token (starting with xapp-*) verification_token STRING empty token to verify the requests (you can find it in the Basic information section) addr STRING &amp;ldquo;:3000&amp;rdquo; address and port in the form IP:PORT socket_mode BOOL false enable the Socket Mode lt_enable BOOL false enable localtunnel for the server lt_baseurl STRING &amp;ldquo;https://localtunnel.</description></item><item><title>Html</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/html/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 23:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/html/</guid><description>Html This filter is used to extract information from an HTML page received through the Message.
Like jQuery for JS, we can set a selector to find in the page, extract text from the tags and the html content (we are using goquery library under the hood).
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be main or an extra field) selector STRING &amp;quot;&amp;quot; the selector to find in the HTML page get STRING &amp;ldquo;html&amp;rdquo; what do we want to retrieve on the tags found in the selected one: html, text, attr attr STRING &amp;quot;&amp;quot; if get is attr you can define what attr name it should extract .</description></item><item><title>Apt</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/apt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 11:38:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/apt/</guid><description>Apt feeder This feeder can create the stream starting from an apt repository. It supports also flat repositories.
It is possible to specify the frequency of the quering and receive a message every time a new package is published.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description url STRING empty URL of the apt repo freq DURATION 60s how often the feed should be parsed suite STRING &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; suite of the repo to keep under control arch STRING empty&amp;quot; architecture of the repo, if empty the first arch returned by the Release file will be used index STRING empty URL of the Packages file (it overrides the url parameter) insecure BOOL false allow repository with insecure certificates .</description></item><item><title>Striptag</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/striptag/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:35:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/striptag/</guid><description>StripTag This filter is used to remove all the HTML tags from a string.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be main or an extra field) ... | striptag(target=&amp;quot;main&amp;quot;) | ...
Output The main of the output Message will have the text extracted from the target config, stripped by all the HTML tags.</description></item><item><title>Timer</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/timer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 18:06:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/timer/</guid><description>Timer feeder This feeder trigger a pipeline every time the timer is fired.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description freq DURATION 60s The intervals (in duration) on how often to execute the pipeline &amp;lt;timer: freq=&amp;quot;30s&amp;quot;&amp;gt; | ...
Output Text The main field of the Message will contain time in rfc3339 format.
Extra Name Description rfc3339 time in rfc3339 format timestamp time in Unix timestamp Examples Soon&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Folder</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/folder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 13:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/folder/</guid><description>Folder feeder This feeder can create the stream of fsnotify events for a given folder or for cloud platform storage like Amazon S3,
Google Drive and Dropbox.
The feeder use cloudwatcher to keep track of changes on the chosen directory.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description name STRING empty the path of the folder that it has to keep track type STRING &amp;ldquo;local&amp;rdquo; the type of service to use local, dropbox, gdrive, s3 or git freq DURATION 2s how often the directory should be checked for updates Some services like Gdrive, S3 and Dropbox require additional configurations (you can check them from here).</description></item><item><title>Slack</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/slack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 19:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/slack/</guid><description>Slack This filter allows you to send files, messages and download files from Slack.
It can be used alone or with the Slack Feeder to create a simple Slack bot for events API.
Parameters The following parameters are required from this filter:
Parameter Type Default Description action STRING &amp;ldquo;send_message&amp;rdquo; action to perform: &amp;ldquo;send_message&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;send_file&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;download_file&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;user_info&amp;rdquo; token STRING &amp;quot;&amp;quot; Slack bot Token Each action can use different parameters:</description></item><item><title>Changed</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/changed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/changed/</guid><description>Changed This filter is similar to the cache. It can only stop the propagation of the Message across the lane, but only if the target of the received Message is different from the previous one.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be main or and extra field) .</description></item><item><title>Echo</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/echo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/echo/</guid><description>Echo This filter prints the Message on the logs. It is mostly used to debug the rules.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description extra BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; print also all the extra fields ... | echo(extra=&amp;quot;false&amp;quot;) | ...
Output The output is not being changed. This filter prints the received Message and send it to the next filter in the rule.</description></item><item><title>Format</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/format/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/format/</guid><description>Format This filter is used to format the received Message. It is based on
the Golang templates and it can load templates from the template_path
directory specified in the configuration file.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description type STRING &amp;ldquo;text&amp;rdquo; specify the type of template to use : &amp;quot;text&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;html&amp;quot; template STRING empty a template could be specified directly here, instead of load it from file file STRING empty load the template from file target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be main or an extra field) In the template is allowed to use all the fields of the received Message: main or extra.</description></item><item><title>Hash</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/hash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/hash/</guid><description>Hash This filter is used to search or extract hashes from a Message.
Supported types of hashes are:
MD5 SHA1 SHA256 SHA512 Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be main or an extra field) extract BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; if &amp;quot;true&amp;quot; the main field of the output Message will be the extracted hash md5 BOOL &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; if &amp;quot;false&amp;quot; md5 hashes will be ignored sha1 BOOL &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; if &amp;quot;false&amp;quot; sha1 hashes will be ignored sha256 BOOL &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; if &amp;quot;false&amp;quot; sha256 hashes will be ignored sha512 BOOL &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; if &amp;quot;false&amp;quot; sha512 hashes will be ignored .</description></item><item><title>Http</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/http/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/http/</guid><description>HTTP This filter allows you to send HTTP requests. When a Message arrives to the filter, we can decide if use the main field of the Message as URL on the request, or its content for the HTTP data.
This behaviour can be handled with the parameters.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description url STRING empty URL of the web page. It is possible use the Golang templates to use fields of the Message download_to STRING empty path of where to download the file.</description></item><item><title>Mail</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/mail/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/mail/</guid><description>Mail This filter allows you to send an e-mail. When a Message arrives to the filter, we can decide if use the main field of the Message as URL on the request, or its content for the HTTP data.
This behaviour can be handled with the parameters.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description body STRING empty the body of the e-mail (supports Golang templates) username STRING empty username for the host authentication password STRING empty password for the host authentication host STRING empty host server used to send the e-mail port STRING empty port of the host server fromAddr STRING empty source e-mail address fromName STRING empty source name address to STRING empty destination e-mail address (supports multi-destination, comma separated) subject STRING empty subject field of the e-mail to send use_auth BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; the sendmail server will receive the credentials specified in username and password fields .</description></item><item><title>MIME type</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/mimetype/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/mimetype/</guid><description>MIME type This filter allows you to detect the MIME type of a file and its extension.
Based on the gabriel-vasile/mimetype library.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be the main or and extra field) filename STRING empty the filename of the file to detect (supports Golang templates) .</description></item><item><title>Override</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/override/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/override/</guid><description>Override This filter allows you to change a field of a Message, before sending it to the next filter. Template can be used.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description name STRING empty name of the field to change (supports Golang templates) value STRING empty new value to assign to the Message&amp;rsquo;s field specified (supports Golang templates) ... | override(name=&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;, value=&amp;quot;{{ .</description></item><item><title>Pdf</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/pdf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/pdf/</guid><description>Pdf This filter allows you to extract plain text from a PDF file.
Based on the ledongthuc/pdf library.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be the main or and extra field) filename STRING empty the filename of the PDF file to parse (supports Golang templates) .</description></item><item><title>Random</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/random/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/random/</guid><description>Random This filter is used to inject an extra field with a random number in the propagated Message.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description output STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the propagated Message that will contain the random number min STRING &amp;ldquo;0&amp;rdquo; the min value of the extracted number is min max STRING &amp;ldquo;999999&amp;rdquo; the max value of the extracted number is max .</description></item><item><title>System</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/system/</guid><description>System This filter allows you to exec a command on the host machine. The received Message can be used to create the command to launch.
It supports Golang templates (only text.Template).
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description cmd STRING empty command line to exec for each received Message (supports Golang templates) ... | system(cmd=&amp;quot;echo '{{ .author }} wrote {{ .main }}' &amp;gt;&amp;gt; logs.</description></item><item><title>Text</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/text/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/text/</guid><description>Text This filter searches or extracts strings from the received Message. It can be used with a regular expression or a simple string.
If the string is found, the condition is matched and the Message is propagated to the next filter.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be main or and extra field) regexp BOOL false the pattern field is a regular expression extract BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; the main field of the propagated Message will contain the extracted string (it can be used only if regexp parameter is set true) pattern STRING empty specifies the pattern that should be matched on the Message to check the condition .</description></item><item><title>Url</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/url/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/url/</guid><description>Url This filter is used to search or extract URLs from a Message.
Currently supported types of URLs are:
http/s ftp Parameters Parameter Type Default Description target STRING &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; the field of the Message that should be used for the filter (it could be main or an extra field) http BOOL &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo;, http scheme urls are ignored https BOOL &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo;, https scheme urls are ignored ftp BOOL &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo;, ftp scheme urls are ignored extract BOOL &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo;, the main field of the propagated Message will contain the found URL .</description></item></channel></rss>