<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>JS on Dripline Documentation</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/</link><description>Recent content in JS on Dripline Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Basics</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/basics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/basics/</guid><description>JS This filter allows to extend the basic driplane&amp;rsquo;s filter, defining Javascript scripts. It is based on islazy/plugin that is based on robertkrimen/otto.
Defining a JS file with our custom logic, it is possible create a complex filter.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description path STRING empty path of the Javascript file (it can contains multiple functions) function STRING empty name of the function in the JS file to call when a Message is received .</description></item><item><title>Entrypoint</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/entrypoint/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/entrypoint/</guid><description>Entrypoint The JS file should consist of one or more functions, and they can be used in different filters or in combination between them.
The function has to respect some constraints:
the function&amp;rsquo;s name contained in the function parameter of the filter has to start with a capital letter; the function prototype should accept 3 variables; the function has to return a JS object with at least the filtered field; Function&amp;rsquo;s prototype The function&amp;rsquo;s name specified in the function parameter of the filter, receives 3 input parameters:</description></item><item><title>Plugin Packages</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/packages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/filters/js/packages/</guid><description>Packages Since the JS doesn&amp;rsquo;t have all the useful functions to perform operations like on file manipulation or http request (see otto docs for more info), driplane maps and export to the JS environment some Go functions as packages.
These mapped functions are not definitive and they could change over time. File This package contains functions for manipulating files.
Return The return value will be a JS object containing 2 fields:</description></item></channel></rss>