<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Feeders on Dripline Documentation</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/</link><description>Recent content in Feeders on Dripline Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 11:30:07 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>File</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/file/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/file/</guid><description>File feeder This feeder can create the stream starting from a file. Like the tail -f command it opens the specified file and propagates a data message if a line is being added to the file.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description filename STRING empty the path of the file that it has to keep track toend BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; the feeder will start to create data messages only for new added lines .</description></item><item><title>RSS</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/rss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/rss/</guid><description>RSS This feeder create a stream starting from a feed RSS, ATOM or JSON.
It is based on gofeed so you can refer to it for more info and supported formats.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description url STRING empty URL of the feed freq DURATION 60s how often the feed should be parsed start_from_beginning BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; start to parse from the beginning of the feed .</description></item><item><title>Twitter</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/twitter/</guid><description>Twitter This feeder creates a stream from tweets. It is possible to define the keywords, or the users to follow.
Based on go-twitter
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description consumerKey STRING empty Twitter Auth consumerSecret STRING empty Twitter Auth accessToken STRING empty Twitter Auth accessSecret STRING empty Twitter Auth keywords STRING empty comma separated keywords that should match on the tweets users STRING empty comma separated users list languages STRING empty filter by language disable_retweet BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; don&amp;rsquo;t include retweets in the stream disable_quoted BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; don&amp;rsquo;t include quoted tweets in the stream .</description></item><item><title>Web</title><link>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/web/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 22:38:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://matrix86.github.io/driplane/doc/feeders/web/</guid><description>Web This feeder creates a stream starting from a web page. It is possible to define how often the page should be downloaded and parsed.
Every time the page is parsed a Message is sent down the lane.
Parameters Parameter Type Default Description url STRING empty URL of the web page freq DURATION 60s how often the page should be parsed text_only BOOL &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; if &amp;ldquo;true&amp;rdquo; it removes all the tags from the page method STRING &amp;ldquo;GET&amp;rdquo; HTTP method to use on the requests headers JSON empty Headers to use in the request data JSON empty POST fields to send with the requests (it&amp;rsquo;s not possible to use in combination with rawData) rawData STRING empty raw body of the requests (it&amp;rsquo;s not possible to use in combination with data) status STRING empty the filter will propagate the Message only if the returned status is this cookies STRING empty Path of the JSON file containing the cookies to use .</description></item></channel></rss>